Okay, let's try something else.
From the beginning. Ready. One, two, three.
One, two, three, checkers. Keep the rhythm.
Okay, it's dai.
One, two, three...
One, two, three, knocks. Keep the rhythm.
Wait a minute! What are you laughing at? It's true, the horse got carried away a little, and that's good!
Look, I remember once my dad took me to a jazz club, and I didn't want to go at all.
But I saw the pianist and he was playing the fourths with an accent.
And then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then!
And then, a minor key, then he added an internal theme and it was like, it was like he sang.
I got dirty the next thing I saw was like chili, it swept onto the stage.
He was lost in the music, he was in it, and he took us all there.
And I wanted to learn to speak like that.
That's when I realized I was born to play.
Connie understands me. Don't you, Connie?
I am 12.
I'm coming back now. Practice the scales.
Excuse me for interrupting the class.
No worries, you're good.
Not.
How can I help, Director Roy?
I wanted to personally tell you the good news.
You are no longer a paid employee, but the conductor of the Polenstadt orchestra.
Secure job, medical insurance, pension.
That's great.
Welcome to the 70th School family, Joe.
Permanently.
Thanks to.
Come on.
After so many years, my prayers were heard.
Work of Fullstadt.
We have workshops, great.
Yes, Mom, but I...
You're going to tell them yes, right?
No need, Mom, I have a plan.
You don't have a plan.
Maybe you also need a backup plan for when your plan fails.
We can educate you to become a middle-aged man who washes himself in a dyed-in-the-wool toilet.
And walk around with a hole in my pants.
Yes, but...
With this job, you will be able to put an end to random commitments.
Everyone knows we need more teachers.
Just in thoughts. Music will finally become your real career.
You're going to tell them yes. Right?
Please say yes.
Yes, of course.
Okay.
Hello?
How are you, Mr. G? It's Rochelle. Lamont, Lamont Baker.
Hello, Rochelle! It's good to hear your voice.
Yeah, look, you can call me Joe Rocheleau. I'm not your teacher anymore.
Okay, Mr. Garner. Here's what?
I am the new drummer in Dorothea Williams' whirlwind.
and we start the tour from half a note until dinner.
Dorothea Williams, are you kidding? Congratulations, boy!
I would die a happy man,
if I could play with Dorothea Williams.
Today is the happy day.
Okay!
Here it is! Hello, Rochelle!
Leon, deserted city. This is not much of a problem.
Yes, obviously. I'm glad you came.
Yes, he played with you last year in Brooklyn.
She thinks you're great.
You know, we played in a cafe, right?
Hey, Dorothea!
This is the man I was telling you about.
The conductor of our school orchestra, Mr. Gardner.
Call me Joe Dorothea.
I mean, I meant Miss Williams.
It's an honor for me.
Wow, that's great.
Joe is Ray Gardner's son.
Oh, we got to the school conductor.
Well, come on, teacher.
We don't have all day.
What are you, Rome?
Tori, Tori, Tori.
Sorry, I got a little carried away.
Joe Gardnar, where have you been?
Well, I led the school orchestra, but on the weekends...
Do you have a suit?
From...
Find yourself a suit, a nice suit.
Well, buddy, see you tonight, the show is at 9, the sauna at 7.
Then we will hear you.
Yes!
Woo-hoo!
Life is a beautiful card!
Oh, that's glorious!
Well, go ahead, go ahead!
Do you know where it might be written there?
Joe Gardnar!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You have to believe what's happening!
I did it!
Everyone is my hips!
Yes!
Yes, I know, I know!
Dorothea Wieners!
Can you imagine?
Hey, man!
That you greet me!
Just don't tell mom about the goal!
Is that so?
We got lost!
I am the jukebox!
I'm Dorothea Wieners, friend!
Do you understand me?
I am...
I'm sorry!
What?
Echo!
Look at him!
So, how are you?
Copic J is the Force!
How could they give it without a price?!"
But how?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ho!
Oh, hello!
Oh, what's your name, darling?
I'm Joe, Joe Gardner.
Look, I'm not supposed to be here.
Oh, your accident happened suddenly.
Look, Joe, I'm 106 years old now.
I've been waiting for this for a long time.
Who is Velikod Otvod?
Velikod Beyond?
Like... like the afterlife?
Yes.
And that's death over there?
Hey, Viano, you're on a mental health kick.
It's rewarding, isn't it?
No, no, no. Look, I'm not a participant. I can't die now.
I don't think you have a say in the matter.
Yes, yes, I have it.
I won't die the day I get a chance.
It was time. No, I was even late.
I'm getting out of here.
I don't think you're allowed to go here.
You can't be.
I won't die today.
My life has just begun.
What is this? Wait!
I'm not finished, I have to go back.
I don't want to die.
I'm not ready, I'm not ready.
Run! Why don't you run?
No! What's going on?
Murren, today I want.
I'm not ready.
Oh, no, no!
Oh, I think they are!
No, no, no!
I'm not ready!
No, get out!
Oh no!
APPARATIV MELODY
HARDWARE MUSIC
What?
Mel破ossen, what are you doing in the Zone?
Mooney into the nuclei!
I'm tired of it, I need to find a reminder,
fight from two.
What?
Чwo pok nothing potaye?
When you didn't return halfway, I suspected something was wrong.
I came back here and they took it away.
Lost souls are obsessed with something that separates them from life.
But what can haunt a soul that has not lived?
There she is! There! Take a good look!
22!
The network! Now!
Whipped!
That's Peter!
The captain always buys his own food!
The laundry was drowning!
22!
Come back, 22!
I am Cho!
Quietly, 22, quietly!
I'm back!
Just to give you this!
Kloko!
22, listen! Come back!
And for the correction of errors of distraction and justification,
We are now presenting this trophy to you, as you requested.
It is a pleasure for me to accept this award that I requested,
but I absolutely deserve it.
Jockgarder?
I take that back.
Oh, no! You don't belong here!
Aaaaa
Aaa!
22, stop! I have to tell you something...
I was there, at...
Not?
22!
Oh, mothers! I'm getting excited...
Worried... Don't worry.
Oh, don't run, please. Go!
22, stop!
Listen to me, I was wrong!
Listen to me. You're ready to live 22.
Not for long. No. No profit. He has to pay the last debt.
22!
You are dishonest! You always make bad decisions!
You are not wise and will not illuminate a trace.
Nobody wants to be near you.
You always make bad decisions!
You are not wise and will not illuminate a trace.
You will never find a place to stay.
You've got it.
Just don't cover it up.
The following key is 34.
You will never find a place to stay.
It makes no sense.
This is not for goals, go ahead and do it.
It's just ordinary.
This is a waste of time.
You got that bump just because you were in my body.
That's why I'm taking everything off.
Because you have no purpose.
It makes no sense.
You will never find a place to stay.
Because you have no purpose.
Because you won't find a place to stay.
Nothing.
Just to fill the last gap.
I surrender.
Are you ready?
To live.
I'm scared, Joe. I'm not good enough,
And I didn't find my Spark either.
Against.
The spark is not your goal. The last circle,
that it fills up when you are ready to live.
It's that you're great at jazz.
But, Joe, that means you won't...
Don't worry, I've already lived. Now it's your turn.
I will come with you.
You know you can't.
Egger!
Ahaha!
It's that you're awesome.
Mr. Gardner.
Yes?
Can I have a minute?
I think I speak for all of Jerry when I say. Thank you.
For what? Our job is to inspire, Joe.
Is that so?
That's why we decided to give you another chance.
Yes, but watch where you go from now on.
But, ami Terry...
Согласувахме го с Тэрри.
I don't know what you're saying.
It doesn't matter.
Thanks to.
Yes, what are you planning to do? How are you going to spend your life?
I'm not sure.
But...
I will live every minute.
Okay!